[
  {
    "question": "Specialize access routes/interfaces to allow capturing or specification of variable values.",
    "answers": [3],
    "options": ["Availability", "Modifiability", "Performance", "Testability"]
  },
  {
    "question": "Firewalls restrict access based on message source or destination port.",
    "answers": [2],
    "options": ["Modifiability", "Performance", "Security", "Testability"]
  },
  {
    "question": "Limit possible options: Reduce the possible options for variations for modules.",
    "answers": [1],
    "options": ["Availability", "Modifiability", "Performance", "Security"]
  },
  {
    "question": "Spare: A standby spare configured to replace many different failed components.",
    "answers": [0],
    "options": [
      "Availability",
      "Interoperability",
      "Modifiability",
      "Testability"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Polymorphism: Late binding of method calls.",
    "answers": [1],
    "options": ["Availability", "Modifiability", "Security", "Usability"]
  },
  {
    "question": "Bound execution times: Place a limit on how much execution time is used to respond to an event.",
    "answers": [2],
    "options": ["Availability", "Modifiability", "Security", "Usability"]
  },
  {
    "question": "Maintain existing interfaces: Avoid to change interfaces that other modules uses.",
    "answers": [0],
    "options": ["Modifiability", "Performance", "Security", "Usability"]
  },
  {
    "question": "Exceptions: Recognizing faults by raising exceptions when a specified fault occurs.",
    "answers": [0],
    "options": ["Availability", "Modifiability", "Security", "Usability"]
  },
  {
    "question": "Increase available resources: Faster and more processors, more memory, faster network.",
    "answers": [3],
    "options": [
      "Availiability",
      "Interoperability",
      "Modifiability",
      "Performance"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Shadow operation to mimic the behavior of the working components before restoring service.",
    "answers": [0],
    "options": ["Availability", "Modifiability", "Performance", "Usability"]
  },
  {
    "question": "Maintain a model of the task: Used to determine context of a system.",
    "answers": [3],
    "options": ["Availability", "Modifiability", "Performance", "Usability"]
  },
  {
    "question": "State resynchronization to upgrade a component to restore its previous state.",
    "answers": [0],
    "options": ["Availability", "Modifiability", "Performance", "Usability"]
  },
  {
    "question": "Configuration files: Intended to set parameters at startup.",
    "answers": [1],
    "options": ["Availability", "Modifiability", "Performance", "Usability"]
  },
  {
    "question": "Authorize users to ensure authenticated users have the rights to access/modify data or services",
    "answers": [2],
    "options": ["Availability", "Modifiability", "Security", "Usability"]
  },
  {
    "question": "Scheduling policy: Scheduling of resources based on priority assignment and dispatching.",
    "answers": [3],
    "options": [
      "Availability",
      "Interoperability",
      "Modifiability",
      "Performance"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Checkpoint/rollback: A recording of a consistent state that can later be restored.",
    "answers": [0],
    "options": ["Availability", "Modifiability", "Performance", "Usability"]
  },
  {
    "question": "Hide information: Make parts of information of a module private and provide interfaces.",
    "answers": [1],
    "options": ["Availability", "Modifiability", "Performance", "Usability"]
  },
  {
    "question": "Authenticate users: Ensuring that a user or remote computer is actually who it claims to be.",
    "answers": [2],
    "options": ["Availability", "Modifiability", "Security", "Usability"]
  },
  {
    "question": "Removal from service to undergo some activities to prevent anticipated failures.",
    "answers": [0],
    "options": [
      "Availability",
      "Interoperability",
      "Modifiability",
      "Performance"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Control frequency of sampling for queued requests possibly resulting in loss of requests.",
    "answers": [3],
    "options": [
      "Availability",
      "Interoperability",
      "Modifiability",
      "Performance"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Maintain a model of the system: Determines the expected system behavior enabling feedback.",
    "answers": [3],
    "options": ["Availability", "Modifiability", "Performance", "Usability"]
  },
  {
    "question": "Maintain integrity using checksums or hash results to allow testing of manipulation of the data",
    "answers": [2],
    "options": ["Availability", "Modifiability", "Security", "Usability"]
  },
  {
    "question": "Heartbeat:Component emits a heartbeat message periodically and another component listens for it",
    "answers": [0],
    "options": [
      "Availability",
      "Interoperability",
      "Modifiability",
      "Performance"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Restrict communication paths: Restrict the modules with which a given module shares data.",
    "answers": [1],
    "options": ["Availability", "Modifiability", "Performance", "Usability"]
  },
  {
    "question": "Adherence to defined protocols: Allows runtime binding of independent processes.",
    "answers": [0],
    "options": ["Availability", "Performance", "Security", "Testability"]
  },
  {
    "question": "Increase computational efficiency to improve algorithm or use cache methods for processor/disk",
    "answers": [2],
    "options": ["Availability", "Modifiability", "Performance", "Usability"]
  },
  {
    "question": "Ping/echo: Component issues a ping and expects to receive back an echo, within predefined time.",
    "answers": [0],
    "options": ["Availability", "Modifiability", "Performance", "Usability"]
  }
]
